Guide to the Jean O'Barr Papers, 1974-2011 RL.00968
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2011-0010), 1964-2005, 8 boxes
  - Correspondence and Planning for Miscellaneous Talks and Projects
    - "Women Imagine Change," University of Tulsa, 2000, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - "On Education and Women," University of Richmond, December 1999-February 2000 (Box 10)
    - On Women's Studies and Feminism, January-April 2000 (Box 10)
    - Women's Studies Ph.D. Planning Conference, April 2000 (Box 10)
    - Women's Studies Articles and Events, May-August 2000 (Box 10)
    - Guest Lecture: Introduction to African Studies, September 2000 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence and Planning, Washington, D.C., 28 September 2000 (Box 11)
    - National Women's Studies Association Journal Board Meeting, 28 September 2000 (Box 11)
    - Annual Founder's Day, 5 October 2000 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Event in Seattle/Colorado, October 2000 (Box 11)
    - Greensboro College NHE Seminar, 21 September 2000 (Box 11)
    - Visit to Cornell University and Ithaca, 18-21 October 2000 (Box 11)
    - The National Council for Research on Women, Philadelphia, 28-29 October 2000 (Box 11)
    - Judy Chicago Lectures, 30 October 2000 (Box 11)
    - The Power of Words, 1 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Hester Baer Introduction, 3 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Panhel Talk, 8 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Durham Council Meeting, 10-11 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Continuing Education Organizational Change, 16-19 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Duke University Model United Nations Security Conference, 17 November 2000 (Box 11)
    - Visit to Santa Fe, New Mexico, 7 December 2000 (Box 11)
    - Wesleyan Teleconference, 11 December 2000 (Box 11)
    - Margaret Humphrey's Baby Shower, 7 January 2001 (Box 11)
    - Center for Teaching, 11 January 2001 and Fall 2004 (Box 11)
    - Visit to New Jersey, 25-26 January 2001 (Box 11)
    - "Questions on the Eve of Leave," Women's Studies Faculty Seminar, 5 February 2001 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Event in Tampa/Orlando, 6-8 February 2001 (Box 11)
    - "Faces of Feminism at Duke" March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Visit to Mexico, February-March 2001 (Box 11)
    - "Women and Power" and Women's Studies Meetings and Recognitions, March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Duke Women's History Month, March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Center for the Education of Women and other events in Michigan, March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Scholars Dinner, 28 March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Graduate and Professional Women's Network Dinner, 29 March 2001 (Box 11)
    - Duke Women's Athletics, 6-8 April 2001 (Box 11)
    - Reunions, 21 April 2001 (Box 11)
    - Durham Celebration for Jean O'Barr, 29 April 2001 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Graduation Ceremony, 12-13 May 2001 (Box 11)
    - LSAT Conference Call, 14 May 2001 (Box 11)
    - Gender Studies, Indiana University, 18-19 April 2001 (Box 11)
    - Indiana University Articles on Gender and Women, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Berea College, 21 June 2001 (Box 11)
    - Athena Society Incorporated Articles, Sarasota, Florida, 27-29 July 2001 (Box 11)
    - Johns Hopkins University and Baltimore, Maryland, 29-31 July 2001 (Box 11)
    - Visit to Denver, 2 August 2001 (Box 11)
    - Duke University Symposium on Interdisciplinary in Honor of Jean O'Barr, September 2001 (Box 11)
    - "Women in the Know," University of Richmond, September 2001 (Box 11)
    - Hear My Story: Women in the Civil Rights Movement Conference, Oglethorpe University, Atlanta, Georgia, 21 September 2001 (Box 11)
    - University of Richmond, 21 September 2001 (Box 11)
    - Pleiffer University, "Women Imagine Change," 28 September 2001 (Box 11)
    - Founder's Day Lunch, 4-5 October 2001 (Box 11)
    - National Women's Studies Association Journal Meeting in Boone, NC, 5-7 October 2001 (Box 11)
    - Indiana University, Installation of Sharon Stephens Brehm as Chancellor, 9-10 October 2001 (Box 11)
    - Encyclopedia of Education, "Women's Studies," 15 October 2001 (Box 11)
    - Ph.D. Conference at Emory University, 12-14 December 2001 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Event in Atlanta, Dara DeHaven, 11 October 2001 (Box 11)
    - Betsy Hansen/Miriam. "Hear My Story" Oglethorpe University, October, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Pedagogy Workshop, 2 November 2001 (Box 11)
    - "Gender in the Classroom" Women in Science and Engineering Lunch, 1 November 2001 (Box 11)
    - "An Inward Journey" Altrusa Book Club of Durham, 1 November 2001 (Box 11)
    - Council on Women's Studies Weekend, 2-4 November 2001 (Box 11)
    - The Women's College Celebration 1930-1972, 8-10 November 2002, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Teaching Breakfast, 10 January 2002 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Event in Charlotte, North Carolina, January 2002 (Box 11)
    - Women's Studies Event in New Canaan, Connecticut, 28-29 January 2002 (Box 12)
    - Gender Matters, Yale University, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
    - Williamette University, 12 February 2002 (Box 12)
    - Women's University Club in Seattle, 2002 (Box 12)
    - Duke Alumnae Reception, Katherine Tennyson, 11 February 2002 (Box 12)
    - Visit to Oregon: Correspondence Dodie Little, 15-17 February 2002 (Box 12)
    - Guest Lecture for Donna Lisker and Stephanie's Class, 27 February 2002 (Box 12)
    - Mary Armstrong's visit, 23-28 March 2002 (Box 12)
    - Women's Studies Visit to New Jersey and other publications, 5-7 April 2002 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence about Honors, 12 April 2002 (Box 12)
    - Women's Studies Reunion at Duke, 16 April 2002 (Box 12)
    - "Movement to Establish Women's Studies" (published), 2 May 2002 (Box 12)
    - Women's Studies Graduation Ceremony, 12 May 2002 (Box 12)
    - Duke Institute for Learning in Retirement 25th Anniversary Celebration, 13 October 2002 (Box 12)
    - Summer Institute on Globalization, Women and Development, June-August 2002 (Box 12)
    - "Women, Wellness, and the Transformation of Health Care," Integrative Health Conference, 11-13 October 2002 (Box 12)
    - McGee and Evers Consulting, Inc., 11 October 2002 (Box 12)
    - Sallie Bingham at Duke, 3-5 November 2002 (Box 12)
    - Joan Marie Johnson at Duke, 19 November 2002 (Box 12)
    - Visit to Williamette University, December 2002 (Box 12)
    - Conference on Ph.D. in Women's Studies in Atlanta, 12-15 December 2002 (Box 12)
    - Intro to African Studies Guest Lecture, 27-29 January 2003 (Box 12)
    - National Women's Studies Association Journal Meeting: on Hawaii 2002-2003 (Box 12)
    - Race and Gender in Global Perspective Symposium, 7-8 February 2003 (Box 12)
    - Visit to Fort Myers, Florida, 12-16 February 2003 (Box 12)
    - Robin Morgan, Duke University Libraries, 5 March 2003 (Box 12)
    - Lewis and Clark College Gender Studies Symposium, 6-16 March 2003 (Box 12)
    - Graduate Student Research Day, 21 March 2003 (Box 12)
    - "Women's Rights as Human Rights: A Global Perspective" University of North Carolina- Wilmington, 27 March 2003 (Box 12)
    - Reproductive Rights Film Festival, 26 March 2003 (Box 12)
    - University of California San Francisco National Center of Excellence in Women's Health, Nancy Milliken MD, 7-8 April 2003 (Box 12)
    - Women's Athletic Scholarship Campaign Committee, March-April 2003 (Box 12)
    - Alumni Weekend, 12 April 2003 (Box 12)
    - National Women's Studies Association 24th Annual Conference, New Orleans, 19-22 June 2003 (Box 12)
    - Program in the Study of Women and Gender, Princeton University, 15-16 May 2003 (Box 12)
    - Travel for Gender Initiative, 20-21 May 2003 (Box 12)
    - Friends of Library Reception, 29 May 2003 (Box 12)
    - "Women in the Know," University of Richmond, 12 December 2003 (Box 12)
    - Abortion: Research, Ethics and Activism Conference, Duke University, 31 October-1 November 2003 (Box 12)
    - Duke Women's Athletics and the Scholarship Campaign Luncheon, "Strength in Numbers", 22 October 2003 (Box 12)
    - "Thinking Differently: A Reader in European Women's Studies" Holland, 3-17 February 2004 (Box 12)
    - Visit to Austria, 15-31 March 2004 (Box 12)
    - Duke Directions Conference, 14 March 2004 (Box 12)
    - Planned Parenthood of Central North Carolina Choice Affairs, Derby Party, 4 May 2004 (Box 12)
    - Visit to Russia, 15-27 June 2004 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Women's Reception Comments, 14 September 2004 (Box 12)
    - "Having Their Say: Women and Electoral Politics," Perkins Library, Duke, September 2004 (Box 12)
    - Duke University Panhellenic Association, Celebration of Women Leaders, 17 November 2004 (Box 12)
    - Working Women's Wednesdays Comments, 23 February 2005 (Box 12)
    - Leadership Development Program for Women, Charlotte, February 2005 (Box 12)
    - Alumni Reunion Weekend, April 2005 (Box 12)
    - "Women, Power and Academic Institutions" Comments, DUMC Department of Cardiology, 12 May 2005 (Box 12)
    - Concept Paper for The Atlantic Philanthropic Service Company, Inc., and Background Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Arts and Sciences Research Council Grants, 1994-2000 (Box 12)
  - Restricted Materials
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted files are CLOSED until 2036.
    - Policy/Personnel files (Box 13)
    - Reviews of Women's Studies Program and Faculty (Box 13)
- Accession (2012-0005) 1915-2011, 12 boxes
  Accession (2012-0005) houses the personal memorabilia of Jean Fox O'Barr and her parents, Jean Steward Fox and Robert Warren Fox. Materials include date books, family albums and scrapbooks, clippings and serial publications, schoolwork, and various correspondences. Box 15 of this series is currently restricted.
  Box 15 is CLOSED until 2065.
  - Jean Fox O'Barr salary and appointment letters at Duke (Box 14)
  - Women's Studies Council directories (Box 14)
  - Jean Steward Fox scrapbook of her civic life (Box 14)
  - Robert Warren Fox scrapbook of his civic life (Box 14)
  - Childhood scrapbook for Jean Fox O'Barr (Box 14)
  - Jean O'Barr calendars, address books, and date books, 1962, 1974, 1984-1990 (Box 14)
  - Personal Journals, 1952-1996 (Box 15)
    CLOSED: This box is closed to research.
  - Jean O'Barr date books, 1990-1999 (Box 16)
  - Jean O'Barr date books,2000-2011 (Box 17)
  - Jean Steward Fox wedding shower album, 1940 (Box 18)
  - Jean Steward Fox scrapbook, 1933-1939 (Box 18)
  - Sound recordings, 1950, 1965 and undated (Box 18)
  - Commercial picture postcards, 1919-1942 and undated (Box 18)
  - Bob and Jean Fox's honeymoon pictures, 1940 (Box 18)
  - Duke University continuing education, 1973-1977 and undated (Box 18)
  - Duke Women's Studies Institute, 1987-1993 and undated (Box 18)
  - Earlham College, 1968, 1969 (Box 18)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Michigan City, IN, 1964-1971 and undated (Box 18)
  - Indiana Trial Lawyers Association, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Institute of World Affairs, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Little 500 Variety Show, 1965 and undated (Box 18)
  - NOLS courses, undated (Box 18)
  - Pacific American Fisheries, Inc., 1935 (Box 18)
  - Pullman-Standard Manufacturing Co., 1943, 1955 and undated (Box 18)
  - Service Civil International, undated (Box 18)
  - Women's Law and Public Policy Fellowship Program, 1991 and undated (Box 18)
  - Theater and concert programs, 1931-1986 and undated (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous brochures and pamphlets, 1915-1968 and undated (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous programs, 1924-1972 and undated (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous prose, poetry, and dramatic excerpts, undated (Box 18)
  - Travel brochures and maps, undated (Box 18)
  - Serial publications- Screams from the Eyrie, 1932 (Box 18)
  - Serial publications- Signs, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Serial Publications- Tobacco Road, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Serial Publications- We and Thee, 1978-1990 (Box 18)
  - General clippings, 1930s-1990s and undated, 8 folders (Box 18)
  - Wedding and engagement clippings, 1940-1977 and undated (Box 18)
  - Carolina friends school, 1982-1989 and undated (Box 18)
  - Chicago World Fair, 1934 and undated, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Children's International Summer Villages (CISV), 1970-1993 and undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Chronical (Duke University), 1981-1987 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Crimson Comet, 1968 and undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Current Events, 1927 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Dr. Norman M. Beatty Hospital Community Services Newsletter, 1973 and undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Duke Alumni Magazine, 1972-1991 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Duke Dialogue, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Duke University Letters, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Earlham College Report, 1968-1970 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Elston Literary Review, undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Fog Horn (Rotary Club of Michigan City, IN), 1988 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Friends Newsletter (Women's Studies at Duke University), 1988-1992 and undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Horseshoe Herald, 1963-1968 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Indiana Daily Student, 1959-1962 (Box 19)
  - Institute Informer (High School Journalism Institute Indiana University), 1959 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Iteriorscapes, 1984 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Life ("National Purpose" series), 1960 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Madison News, 1947-1955, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- News Dispatch (Michigan City, IN), 1958-1991 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- Northwestern University Alumni News, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Parent (Indiana University), 1965 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Presbyterian Newsletter (First Presbyterian Church, Michigan City, IN), 1963-1979 (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Rotarian, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Address books, 1929 and undated (Box 19)
  - Christmas card and gift notebook, 1956-1992 (Box 19)
  - Household notes/notebook, 1935-1957 and undated, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Medical records regarding auto accident in Spain, 1963-1965 (Box 19)
  - Travel logs and itineraries, 1954-1981 and undated (Box 19)
  - YMCA and Jr. Tri-Hi-Y notebook, undated (Box 19)
  - Serial publications- The Center Report (Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development), 1977 (Box 19)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- science, 1950-1954 and undated, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- social studies, 1950-1951 (Box 19)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Summer Camp, 1959 (Box 19)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- unidentified subjects, 1961 and undated (Box 19)
  - Order of Rainbow for Girls, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Parent Teacher Association Yearbooks, 1928-1950 (Box 19)
  - Parker Civic League, 1932, 1933 and undated (Box 19)
  - Parker Senior High School Commencement programs and miscellaneous memorabilia, 1931-1933 and undated (Box 19)
  - Parker Senior High School Pine yearbook, 1931-1933, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Purdue University North Central Commencement program and announcement, 1991 (Box 20)
  - University of Chicago Handbooks, 1933 and undated (Box 20)
  - University of Denver Commencement program, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Juvenile artwork, 1949-1981 and undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Northwestern University Commencement program, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Academic Recognition, 1953-1962 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- Arithmetic, 1950-1954 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- English, writing and spelling, 1950-1952 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- geography, 1952-1953 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Girlscout notebooks, 1953 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox schoolwork- Social Science, 1933-1934, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox- study outlines various subjects, undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox University of Chicago comprehensive exams, 1933 (Box 20)
  - Robert Fox Isaac Elston high school diploma, 1934 (Box 20)
  - Hirsch Junior High School Gleaner yearbook, 1929-1930 (Box 20)
  - Hirsch Junior High School graduation program, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Indiana University baccalaureate and commencement programs, 1964, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Isaac C. Elston Sr. High School commencement and baccalaureate programs, 1960-1968 (Box 20)
  - James H. Bowen High School commencement program, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox English examination, 1933-1934 and undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox history notes, undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox math notes, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox miscellaneous school projects pre-college, 1931 and undated, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox physics notes, undated (Box 20)
  - Jean Stewart Fox political science, undated (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox report cards and class schedules, 1925-1933 (Box 21)
  - Jean Fox Stewart social science examinations, 1932-1933 (Box 21)
  - Carolina Friends School meeting for graduation program, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Chicago Daily News Wide Awake Club, 1928 (Box 21)
  - Duke University M.A. in liberal studies graduation program, 1994 (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox accounting, 1933 (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox biology notes, 1933-1934 (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox biology examinations, 1933 (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox botany, undated (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox civics, undated (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox diary fragments, 1929-1933 (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox diplomas, 1930, 1933 (see oversized folder 1) (Box 21)
  - Jean Stewart Fox English notes, 1929, 1933-1934 and undated, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr University of Edinburgh notes, 1960-1964, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Fox Anniversary, 1965-1989 and undated, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Fox family birthdays, 1941-1992 and undated, folders 1-3 of 5 (Box 21)
  - Fox family birthdays, 1941-1992 and undated, folders 4-5 of 5 (Box 22)
  - Chi Omega Sorority, 1961 and undated (Box 22)
  - Mary T. Clark, undated (Box 22)
  - Tom Colling, 1931 (Box 22)
  - Evangeline Damian, 1953 (Box 22)
  - Ruth and Phil Domries, undated (Box 22)
  - Fred and Gillian Drysdale, 1973, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Eckardt, 1954 (Box 22)
  - Earl N. Fielding, 1959-1960 (Box 22)
  - Sharon Ford, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Carol Fox, 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - Edward and Jane Fox, 1960-1070 and undated (Box 22)
  - Jean Stewart Fox, 1927-1992 and undated (Box 22)
  - Raymond W. Fox, 1933-1958 (Box 22)
  - Robert Fox, 1939-1992 and undated (Box 22)
  - Charles Haynie, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Roy and Verla Hulvey, 1989 (Box 22)
  - Mrs. Lewis F Jagger, undated (Box 22)
  - Mary Ann Kelso, 1959-1960 and undated (Box 22)
  - Harold Knott, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Nell Knox, 1968, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Jean Laidlaw, 1953 (Box 22)
  - Lewis, Picket and Co., 1937 (Box 22)
  - Robert McCarmick, 1950 (Box 22)
  - Ethel Meyers, undated (Box 22)
  - Nettie Moe, 1969 and undated (Box 22)
  - Frances Achurch, 1963-1965 (Box 22)
  - Kingsley Afful, 1967 (Box 22)
  - Charlotte Bauer, 1961 (Box 22)
  - Kate Bolton, 1968 (Box 22)
  - Ruby Ceder, undated (Box 22)
  - Indiana High School University Journalism Institute, 1959 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- health, undated (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- history (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- home economics (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Iowa Test of Educational Development, 1958 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr juvenile artwork, 1948 and undated (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Kinder preference record, 1958 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr schoolwork- Latin, undated (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr miscellaneous college and scholarship application material, 1960 and undated (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr report cards and class schedules, 1948-1965 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr pre-college school projects, undated (Box 22)
  - Indiana University scrapbook, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr Chi Omega Sorority scrapbook, 1960-1961 (Box 22)
  - Jean Fox O'Barr summer in France scrapbook, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Mrs. Robinson and Mrs. Miller, undated (Box 22)
  - Roth, Bill, and David, undated (Box 22)
  - Maribeth Rupsich, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Danny Sawyer, 1957-1960 and undated (Box 22)
  - Betsy Smith, 1966 and undated (Box 22)
  - Wade and Murial Smith, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Richard Snyder, undate (Box 23)
  - Margaret Soutar, 1964 (Box 23)
  - John Stanfield, undated (Box 23)
  - Ida Stollenz, 1954 (Box 23)
  - Effie Suttie, undated (Box 23)
  - Betty and Tom Swan, 1938-1978 and undated (Box 23)
  - Eleanor Swan. 1940, 1956 and undated (Box 23)
  - Marty Swanson, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Dorothy Tilford, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Norma Wantling, 1967, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Kenneth B. Webb, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - Sybil and Earl Willingham, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Unidentified, 1926-1987 and undated (Box 23)
  - Unidentified high school letters, 1958-1969 and undated (Box 23)
  - Duke Documentation, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Helen Jones, 1980s-2004 (Box 23)
  - Students, former and present, 1990-2010, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Extended Family, 1990-2004, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - Friends, 1990-2010, 8 folders (Box 23)
  - Colleagues and Misc, 1990-2010, 5 folders (Box 24)
  - Helen R. Fox, 1967 (Box 24)
  - Raymond M. Fox Jr., 1982 (Box 24)
  - Raymond M. Fox Sr., 1955 (Box 24)
  - Carol M. Schwingendorf, 1960 (Box 24)
  - Agnes Stewart, 1979-1980, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Thomas Stewart, 1969, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - John Edward Tilford, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Halloween, undated (Box 24)
  - Mother's Day, 1982-1993 and undated, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - New Baby, 1941 and undated (Box 24)
  - St. Patrick's Day,undated (Box 24)
  - Thanksgiving, undated (Box 24)
  - Valentine's Day, 1989 and undated (Box 24)
  - Wedding invitations and cards, 1937-1965 and undated (Box 24)
  - Christmas, undated (Box 24)
  - Birthdays, undated (Box 24)
  - Confirmation, undated (Box 25)
  - Easter, 1980-1986 and undated (Box 25)
  - Father's Day, 1982, 1993 and undated, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Get Well, 1987-1989 and undated (Box 25)
  - Grandparent's Day, undated (Box 25)
  - Notes of Condolence, 1994 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1999 and undated, 7 folders (Box 25)
- Accession (2014-0139), 1992-2001; 1 boxes; Includes one "message square" quilt with text and images and two binders of material produced and compiled by friends and colleagues of Professor O'Barr related to the Women's Studies Program at Duke. One binder includes material related to contributors to the Jean Fox O'Barr Teaching endowment including completed surveys and reminscences from these individuals. The other binder includes material documenting the creation of the quilt as well as letters of tribute to Professor O'Barr by students, colleagues, family, friends, and other admirers.
  - Quilt with 2 binders of information, 1992-2001 (Box 26)
- Accession (2014-0178), 1928-2012; 3 boxes
  - Speeches, 1976-2012 (Box 27)
    - Family letters, 1928-2010 (Box 28-29)
- Women's Studies Program records
  - Paper Draft, Feminist Scholarship, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Spencer Foundation Conference, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Ageing References, 1998-2001 (Box 31)
  - Letters of Recommendation by O'Barr, 1984-1996; 13 folders (Box 31)